http://www.team24.co.uk/cookie-policy/

News
If you choose to reject all cookies using your browser settings, you may not be able to use Team 24 Ltd products, services and/or websites that require you to log in. However, many Team 24 Ltd online services do not require that you accept cookies.
Please note that if you choose to continue with use of this website without taking any further action in relation to cookies, we will consider that you agree to the use of cookies as described below.
Team 24's Use of Cookies
When you use this website, cookies are set and accessed by or on behalf of Affinity Workforce for a number of purposes, including to:
access your information when you "sign in" to a Team24 website
keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Affinity Workforce's services;
estimate and report our total audience size and traffic;
conduct research to improve Team 24's content and services; and/or
Affinity Workforce does not use cookies to target advertising or to share information with social networking sites or other services.
Google Analytics Cookies
In addition, Team 24 uses Google Analytics to help analyse how users use our websites. This analytical tool uses a cookie set by Google to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the Google analytics cookie about your use of any website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google, and used to evaluate and compile statistical reports about this use for Team 24.
Team 24 will not (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or collect any personally identifiable information about users of our sites, and will not associate any data gathered by means of the Google statistical tool with any personally identifying information.
You can find more information about cookies by visiting www.allaboutcookies.org or www.youronlinechoices.eu
Register Today
Get an instant eligibility decision with our online application form.
Copyright Team24 2018 - Site designed & Built by Venn Digital
Team24 notices:
Could technology be a cure for patient and nursing challenges in the NHS?
Why being a midwife is more than just delivering babies
Are you suited to a career as a paramedic?
Ref:
×
Register Your Details
{{message}}
Permanent
Temporary (full time)
Temporary (part time)
Email Address:
ODP (Anaesthetics/Recovery)
ODP (Scrubs)
Theatre Nurse (Anaesthetics/Recovery)
Theatre Nurse (Scrubs)
Health Carer (with hospital experience)
Health Carer (no hospital experience)
Support Worker
Home Care (Live in)
Upload CV
{{cv_file_name}}
Select a file
By signing up, you agree to our Terms & Conditions as well as our Privacy Policy
I want to opt in to have marketing information sent from Team 24
Temporary (full time)
Temporary (part time)
ODP (Anaesthetics/Recovery)
ODP (Scrubs)
Theatre Nurse (Anaesthetics/Recovery)
Theatre Nurse (Scrubs)
Health Carer (with hospital experience)
Health Carer (no hospital experience)
Support Worker
Home Care (Live in)
Upload CV
{{cv_file_name}}
Select a file
By signing up, you agree to our Terms & Conditions as well as our Privacy Policy
I want to opt in to have marketing information sent from Team 24
Temporary (full time)
Temporary (part time)
ODP (Anaesthetics/Recovery)
ODP (Scrubs)
Theatre Nurse (Anaesthetics/Recovery)
Theatre Nurse (Scrubs)
Health Carer (with hospital experience)
Health Carer (no hospital experience)
Support Worker
Home Care (Live in)
Upload CV
{{cv_file_name}}
Select a file
By signing up, you agree to our Terms & Conditions as well as our Privacy Policy
I want to opt in to have marketing information sent from Team 24
Forgot your password?
Cancel
×
SEND PASSWORD REMINDER
Please enter the email you used to register with us and we will send you a password reminder.
